http://www.colormountain.com/terms/

TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SERVICE - PRIVACY POLICY
WEB SITE TERMS OF USE This Site at COLORMOUNTAIN.COM is fully controlled and operated by Enfo LLC.
These "Terms of Use" set forth the terms and conditions that apply to your use of Colormountain.com (the "Web Site"). By using the Web Site (other than to read this page for the first time), you agree to comply with all of the Terms of Use set forth herein. The right to use the Web Site is personal to you and is not transferable to any other person or entity.
Copyrights and Trademarks A.
All materials contained on the Web Site are Copyright January 01, 2006, Enfo LLC. All rights reserved.
B.
No person is authorized to use, copy or distribute any portion the Web Site including related graphics.
C.
Enfo LLC and other trademarks and/or service marks (including logos and designs) found on the Web Site are trademarks/service marks that identify Colormountain.com and the goods and/or services provided by Enfo LLC. Such marks may not be used under any circumstances without the prior written authorization of Enfo LLC.
Termination
You may terminate your membership at any time. We may terminate your membership for any reason, at any time. Inluding but not limited to the sharing of account information. If you are using a paid version of the Service, and we terminate your membership in the Service because you have breached this Agreement, you will not be entitled to any refund of unused subscription fees. Even after membership is terminated.
Contests, sweepstakes and other Activities
COLORMOUNTAIN.COM provides Rules of Participation for certain activities on this Site including, without limitation, contests and sweepstakes conducted by COLORMOUNTAIN.COM and those in conjunction with third parties. This Agreement is incorporated by reference to the specific Rules of Participation which appear in connection with information about a particular activity. To the extent that any conflict exists between this Agreement and specific Rules of Participation, the Rules of Participation for the activity in which you choose to participate shall govern.
Links to Third-Party Web Site
Colormountain.com may provide hyperlinks to third-party web sites as a convenience to users of the Web Site. Enfo LLC does not control third-party web sites and is not responsible for the contents of any linked-to, third-party web sites or any hyperlink in a linked-to web site. Enfo LLC does not endorse, recommend or approve any third-party web site hyperlinked from the Web Site. Enfo LLC will have no liability to any entity for the content or use of the content available through such hyperlink.
No Representations or Warranties; Limitations on Liability
The information and materials on the Web Site could include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically made to the information contained herein. Enfo LLC MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO ANY INFORMATION, MATERIALS OR GRAPHICS ON THE WEB SITE, ALL OF WHICH IS PROVIDED ON A STRICTLY "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO ANY INFORMATION, MATERIALS OR GRAPHICS ON THE WEB SITE, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THE SITE OWNER OR PUBLISHER BE LIABLE UNDER ANY THEORY OF RECOVERY, AT LAW OR IN EQUITY, FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, SPECIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF USE OR LOST PROFITS), ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY MANNER CONNECTED WITH THE USE OF INFORMATION OR SERVICES, OR THE FAILURE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION OR SERVICES, FROM THE WEB SITE.
Changes to These Terms of Use
Enfo LLC reserves the right to change these Terms of Use at any time by posting new Terms of Use at this location. You can send e-mail to Enfo LLC with any questions relating to these Terms by visiting the contact page.
WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY
1.
Overview
Thank you for visiting Colormountain.com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. We may use the information you provide to contact you about offers and contests. At any time you may opt out of mailings by sending us an email. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Web Site.
2.
What Type of Information We Collect
The server on which the Web Site is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, and the pages and images requested.
3.
Children's Issues
The Web Site is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and children under such age must not use the web site or services offered on it to submit any individually identifiable information about themselves.
4.
Copyright
The materials found on the Web Site are protected by United States and other copyright laws, except for works of the United States Government pursuant to 1 U.S.C. Section 105. The selection, arrangement and presentation of all materials (including information in the public domain), and the overall design of the Web Site are copyright © January 01, 2005, Enfo LLC. Permission is granted to view and print materials from Colormountain.com for the non-commercial purpose of viewing, reading and retaining for reference. Any other copying, distribution, retransmission or modification of information or materials on this site, whether in electronic or hard copy form, without the express prior written permission of Enfo LLC, is strictly prohibited.
5.
No Warranties
Colormountain.com DOES NOT MAKE ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE) WITH REGARD TO THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS, ANY PRODUCTS, INFORMATION OR SERVICE PROVIDED THROUGH THE WEB SITE, OR ANY SITES LISTED THEREIN, AND THE WEB SITE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY COST OR DAMAGE ARISING EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY FROM ANY SUCH TRANSACTION. THE WEB SITE DOES NOT WARRANT THAT IT WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT DEFECTS IN IT WILL BE CORRECTED. THE WEB SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS, AS AVAILABLE" BASIS.
IN NO EVENT WILL THE WEB SITE OR ITS MEMBERS, MANAGERS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS AND THE ASSIGNS OF SAME BE LIABLE FOR (1) ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR INFORMATION, AND THE LIKE) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS OR ANY INFORMATION, OR TRANSACTIONS PROVIDED ON THE WEB SITE OR DOWNLOADED FROM THE WEB SITE, EVEN IF THE WEB SITE OR ITS AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR (2) ANY CLAIM ATTRIBUTABLE TO ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THE WEB SITE, THE MATERIALS AND/OR LISTINGS OR INFORMATION DOWNLOADED THROUGH THE WEB SITE. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE WEB SITE'S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
6.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Web Site and its members, managers, officers, employees, agents and the assigns of same, from and against any and all loss, costs, expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees and expenses), claims, damages and liabilities related to or associated with your use of the Web Site and any violation of this Privacy Policy by you.
7.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Privacy Policy constitutes a contract made under and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of
Michigan.
8.
Last Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 27, 2009.
9.
Contact Information
Questions or comments regarding the Web Site should be sent by e-mail available at the contact page.
Copyright 2005-2020 ColorMountain.com All Rights Reserved. Contact | Give-A-Way Sign Up | Unsubscribe | Terms of Service | Kids Eat Free
